阿諾·施瓦辛格
鐵 血 戰 士
你看來很精神  達奇
You're looking good, Dutch.
很久不見了  將軍
It's been a long time, General.
進去裡面談吧
Come on inside.
18小時前
Eighteen hours ago,
我們在這小國失去一架直升機
we lost a chopper carrying a cabinet minister
上面載著內閣成員及其助理
and his aide from this charming little country.
收到的訊號顯示  他們的位置大約在這裡
We've got a transponder fix on their position about here.
這位內閣成員...
This cabinet minister...
喜歡亂竄嗎
does he always travel on the wrong side of the border?
是直升機偏離原定航道
Apparently they strayed off course...
他們肯定落入了遊擊隊手中
and we're fairly certain they're in guerrilla hands.
為什麼不用正規部隊去營救他們
Why don't you use the regular army?
而要用我們這些特種部隊
What do you need us for?
因為有笨蛋認為你們是最好的  指定要你們
'Cause some damned fool accused you of being the best.
狄龍!  你這賤人...
Dillon! You son of a bitch!
怎麼了?
What's the matter?
CIA讓你坐太久辦公室嗎?
The CIA got you pushing too many pencils?
夠了嗎?
Had enough?
你可以放輕鬆些的
Make it easy on yourself, Dutch.
好吧...好吧...好吧!
OK! OK, OK.
你永遠不知什麼時候該停
You never knew when to quit.
真高興又見到你!
Damn good to see you.
你這條領帶算是什麼?
What's this fucking tie business?
算了  別談我的領帶啦
Come on. Forget about my tie.
我聽說你在柏林的那次任務
I heard about that job you pulled in Berlin.
完美漂亮  達奇
Very nice, Dutch.
就像美好的舊時光
Good old days.
是啊  美好的舊時光
Yeah, I like the good old days.
為什麼你不參加利比亞的那次行動?
Then how come you passed on Libya?
轟炸不是我喜歡的作戰方式
That wasn't my style.
你可沒有特定的作戰方式
You got no style. You know that.
別這樣告訴我
Come on.
你為什麼不肯參加呢?
Why did you pass?
我們是拯救小組...
We're a rescue team...
而不是暗殺小組
not assassins.
我們這次的任務是什麼?
Now, what do we got to do?
這位內閣成員
The cabinet minister's important
對我們在這地區很重要
to our scope of operations in this part of the world.
達奇  將軍的意思是說...
The general's saying a couple of our friends are about to get squeezed.
我們不能讓他們被害
We can't let that happen.
我們需要最好的小組
We need the best.
這就是你的小組在此的原因
That's why you're here.
繼續說
Go on.
很簡單的行動  一天就能搞定
Simple setup. One-day operation.
我們到直升機那裡尋找遊擊隊的足跡
We pick up their trail at the chopper, grab those hostages,
救出人質  在他們發現之前
and bounce back, and cross the border...
我們已經越過邊境回來
before anybody knows we were there.
"我們"是什麼意思
What do you mean, "we"?
我跟你們一起行動
I'm going in with you, Dutch.
將軍  你知道我的隊伍一向是單獨行動的
General, my team always works alone. You know that.
抱歉  少校  我們各有各的命令
We all have our orders, Major.
一旦完成任務後
Once you reach your objective...
狄龍將接管這次行動
Dillon will evaluate the situation and take charge.
目的地已標在地圖上  無線電頻道也已調好
Rendezvous points and radio freqs are indicated and fixed.
每四小時跟指揮部聯絡一次
AWACs contact on four-hour intervals.
誰是我們的支援?
Who's our backup?
沒有支援  老朋友
No such thing, ol' buddy.
這是單程任務
This is a one-way ticket.
我們越過邊界  一切就只能靠自己
Once we cross that border, we're on our own.
這任務越聽越有趣
This is getting better by the minute.
比利!  有天我去我女朋友那裡...
Hey, Billy. The other day, I went up to my girlfriend.
我對她說  "我想跟你做愛"
I said, l'd like a little pussy.
她說  "我也是  我的跟房子一樣大"
She said, "Me, too. Mine's as big as a house!"
知道嗎  她希望性器小  因為她的...
See, she wanted a littler one 'cause hers was...
跟房子一樣大...
big as a house.
把那噁心的煙草拿遠一點
Get that stinking shit out of my face, will ya?
都是愚蠢的無能弱者
Bunch of slack-jawed faggots around here!
煙草可令你跟我一樣
This stuff will make you a damn sexual tyrannosaurus
成性超人
just like me.
塞到屁眼裡去吧  佈雷
Yeah? Strap this on your sore ass, Blain.
這打火機是72年在北越
That was in '72.
我跟達奇各得一個作獎勵
Me and Dutch both got one.
嚼煙草真的是個很噁心的習慣
That's a real nasty habit you got there.
到了
Right.
你知道我多懷念跟你一起戰鬥
Never knew how much I missed this, Dutch.
你啥時有這麼聰明了
You never were that smart.
霍金斯  去吧!
Hawkins, you're up.
準備好了
Lines away.
直升機是頭部中彈的
The pilots have each got one round in the head.
他們搶走了裡面所有東西
Whoever hit it, stripped the shit out of it.
遊擊隊是用熱導彈把它擊落
Took him out with a heat-seeker.
還有  少校
Something else, Major.
什麼事?
Ehn?
這不是一架普通的直升機
This is no ordinary army taxi.
在我看來更像偵查機
It looks more like a surveillance bird to me.
找到他們留下的足跡了嗎?
Pick up the trail yet?
比利正在找
Billy's on it.
狄龍  這事越來越複雜
Heat-seeker, Dillon.
遊擊隊怎麼會有熱導彈
That's pretty sophisticated for half-assed mountain boys.
少校
Major
我想他們的裝備越來越好了
I guess they're getting better equipped every day.
原來有12個人
There were 12 guerrillas.
遊擊隊把他們從直升機捉走
They took the two men from the helicopter...
但是  還有別的足跡...
but there's something else.
什麼意思?
What?
有六個穿美國陸軍軍鞋的人
Six men wearing US-issued army boots.
他們是從北方來的
They came in from the north
他們一路追蹤那些遊擊隊
and then they followed the guerrillas.
這事你知道嗎?
Mean anything to you?
可能只是另一組遊擊隊罷了
Probably just another rebel patrol.
他們經常在這一帶出沒
They operate in here all the time.
-你去看看能發現些什麼  -是  長官
-See what you can find. -Yes, sir.
比利找到什麼?
What's he got?
跟以前的一樣
Same business.
遊擊隊捉走了兩個人
Guerrillas hauling two guys in the chopper...
被一些穿美軍裝備的人追蹤
followed by men with American equipment.
還記得上次在阿富汗嗎?
Do you remember Afghanistan?
嘗試把它忘記吧!  來
Trying to forget it. Come on. Let's go.
聖母瑪麗亞...
Holy mother of God.
吉米·霍普
"Jim Hopper."
麥克  將他們放下來
Mac, cut them down.
我認得他是北卡州部隊的
I knew these men. Green Berets out of Fort Bragg.
他們來這裡做什麼?
What the hell were they doing here?
我不知道  達奇
I don't know, Dutch.
這太不人道了!
This is inhuman.
沒有人告訴我這區域有活動
Nobody told me there was an operation in this area.
他們不應該在這裡
They shouldn't have been here.
是有人派他們來的
Well, somebody sent them.
遊擊隊把他們剝皮?
The guerrillas skinned them?
他們為什麼要這樣做?
Why did they skin them?
軍人不應是這樣死法的
Ain't no way for no soldier to die.
比利  到底發生什麼事?
What happened here, Billy?
很奇怪  少校
Strange, Major.
這裡曾經發生槍戰
There was a fire fight.
他們向四面八方盲目射擊
They were shooting in all directions.
我無法想像吉米會走進埋伏
Can't believe Jim Hopper walked into an ambush.
我不相信他中了埋伏
I don't believe he did.
我找不到半點痕跡
I can't find a single track.
完全沒有道理
Just doesn't make sense.
霍普其他的隊員呢?
What about the rest of Hopper's men?
沒有他們的蹤跡
There's no sign, sir.
他們根本沒有離開這裡
They never left here.
他們就像突然消失了一樣
Hell, it's like they just disappeared.
繼續追蹤遊擊隊的足跡  我們去救人質
Stick with the guerrilla trail. Let's get the hostages.
出發吧
We move,
每個人隔5公尺  不要作聲!
five-meter spread. No sound.
是時候把武器拿出來了
It's time to let Old Painless out of the bag.
血債血償的時間
Payback time.
你這討厭的傢伙在做什麼?
You're ghostin' us, mother fucker.
我不管你有多重要
I don't care who you are back in the world.
如果你再不小心暴露行蹤
You give our position one more time...
我會神不知鬼不覺的讓你流血
I'll bleed you real quiet
讓你留下來等死
and leave you here.
你聽清楚了嗎?
Got that?
他們殺了一個人質!
He killed one of the hostages.
我們準備進攻
We move.
麥克和佈雷對付機槍堡
Mac, Blain...the nest.
比利和賓對付警衛
Billy, Poncho...the guard.
霍金斯和狄龍作支援
Hawkins, Dillon...backup.
一切佈署好後  我便攻擊他們的燃料庫
Once they're set, I hit the fuel dump.
解決了一個
One down.
他在做什麼?
What the hell's he doing?
搞什麼?
What the fuck?
表演時間到
Show time, kid.
目標是中央那房屋
Target's the center, on the upper level!
小心九點方向!
Dutch, on your nine!
解決那個!
Get that mother!
釘在此處吧
Stick around.
人質在裡面
Hostages are inside!
你好嗎?
Knock knock.
我去追截他們
I got 'em !
霍金斯  通知指揮部我們現在的位置及狀況
Hawkins, call in position and situation.
用無線電跟指揮部聯絡
Get Connor for the hook!
知道  少校!
You got it, Major.
該死
Shit.
麥克
Mac,
找到其他的人質嗎?
any sign of the other hostage?
找到另外一個  也已經死了
Found the other guy. He's dead, too...
還找到從直升機拆下的齒輪
and the kid from the chopper.
如果他們是中美洲人  那我就是中國人了
But if they're Central American, l'm a Goddamn Chinaman.
這樣說那閣員應是CIA
From the looks of it, our cabinet minister was CIA.
還有  我們運氣不錯
Another thing, Major. We were lucky.
除了遊擊隊外  還有蘇聯軍事顧問
Other guys we waxed...Russian military advisers.
看來有大規模軍事計畫進行
Something pretty big was gonna happen here.
做得好  麥克
Good work, Mac.
清理一下現場  不要留下蛛絲馬跡
Clear the area. No traces.
叫大家準備離去
Get the men ready to move.
好的
Right.
那雜種待在那裡死也不走開
Son of a bitch is dug in like an Alabama tick.
你中了彈  在流血!
You're hit. You're bleeding, man.
我沒時間流血
I ain't got time to bleed.
好吧
Oh...OK.
有時間躲一躲嗎?
You got time to duck?
真他媽漂亮!
This is goddamn beautiful.
中正頭獎!
Goddamn jackpot.
比想像中更多機密!
This is more than we ever thought we'd get.
給我們一網打盡
Now we got those bastards.
捉個正著
We got 'em.
我想這才是你要找的東西
I think this is what you're looking for.
你利用我們!
You set us up!
你告訴我的都是廢話  你騙我們!
It's all bullshit! All of it.
什麼內閣成員等等...
The cabinet minister, the whole business.
騙我們來這裡替你賣命
Got us in here to do your dirty work.
我們剛阻止一次大型入侵
We just stopped a major invasion.
他們本來三天內便會侵略
In three days, they'd have crossed the border with the stuff.
為什麼挑我們?
Why us?
沒其他人能完成這任務
Because nobody else could've pulled it off.
騙你是因為不這樣的話你不會來
You're pissed about the cover story? I needed it to get you in here.
那你告訴霍普什麼樣的故事
What story did you hand Hopper?
我們花了幾個月才找到這裡
Look, we've been looking for this place for months.
那架直升機被擊中時  我的手下在裡面
My men were in that chopper when it got hit!
霍普是要來拯救我的手下
Hopper was supposed to get them.
而他卻不見了
He disappeared.
他沒有失蹤  他是被活活的剝了皮
He didn't disappear. He was skinned alive!
而我的命令就是  送能消滅兇手的人到這裡
My orders were to get somebody to crack these bastards!
所以你編故事騙我們來送死
So you cooked up a story and dropped us in a meat grinder.
你是怎麼了  狄龍?
What happened to you, Dillon?
你以前是個值得信賴的人啊!
You used to be somebody I could trust.
我清醒了
I woke up.
你為什麼不能醒過來?
Why don't you?
你是項資產...
You're an asset...
一項可以犧牲的資產
an expendable asset...
我用你來完成任務
and I used you to get the job done.
明白嗎?
Got it?
我的手下不是可以隨便犧牲的!
My men are not expendable.
我也不做這種事!
And I don't do this kind of work.
少校!  少校!
Major! Major!
我們有麻煩!
We stepped into some real shit here.
空中偵查說到處都是遊擊隊
Air surveillance says we got guerillas all over the place.
就在一兩公里範圍內
Can't be more than one, two miles away.
他們大概多久會到?
How much time?
半個小時內
Half hour, maybe less.
告訴麥克  五分鐘後出發
Tell Mac we move in five.
等一等  她跟我們一起走
Wait. She goes with us.
她非常有價值
She's too valuable.
她一定知道整個部署
She's got the whole of that work.
她一有機會便會洩露我們行蹤
She'll give away our position any chance she gets.
不行!
No deal.
少校  你必須聽我命令
You're still under orders, Major.
你下命令還是由我來?
You wanna make that call or should I?
你自己負責看著她
She's your baggage.
你跟不上的話  便自理
You fall behind, and you're on your own.
直升機在這裡升降太危險
Place is too hot for a pickup.
他們不會在這裡接我們  除非我們越過邊境
They won't touch us till we get over the border.
比利!  哪條路可以離開這裡
Hey, Billy, give me a way out of this hole.
空中偵查說我們被包圍
Aerial says we're cut off.
唯一的出路是那山谷  它會把我們引向東邊
The only way out is that valley that leads east...
那條路非常險峻
but I wouldn't wish that on a broke-dick dog.
我們沒得選擇
Not much choice.
賓  你開路  儘快前進!
Poncho, take lead. Double-time it.
放開我
還有很長的路要走
你給我乖一點
狄龍
Dillon!
狄龍  過來
Dillon! Over here.
轉身
Turn around.
為什麼?
Why?
謝謝!
Thanks.
好說!
Anytime.
比利!
Billy! Billy!
有天我對女朋友說
The other day, I was going down on my girlfriend...
你的性器很大
and I said to her"Jeez, you got a big pussy.
你的性器很大...
Jeez, you got a big pussy."
她問為什麼要說兩次
She said, "Why did you say that twice?"
我說我沒有說兩次啊!
And I said, "l didn't."
明白嗎?  因為洞太大  有回音...
See, it was because of the echo. It was...
這裡  這裡...
Over here. Over here. Over here.
轉身  轉身
Turn around. Turn around.
轉身  轉身  這裡
Turn around. Turn around. Over here.
好說
Anytime.
他媽的!
Goddamn. Whew.
老兄
Buddy, buddy, buddy.
我以前也去過可怕的叢林  但都比不上這裡
I've seen some bad-ass bush before, but nothing like this.
同意  這地方真是怪異
I hear you. This shit's something.
柬埔寨和這比  都成天堂了
Makes Cambodia look like Kansas.
喝點這個吧
Que pasa, amigo?
有點家的味道!
A little taste off home.
在這種地方失去自我控制  就麻煩了
You lose it here, you're in a world of hurt.
不要拖延我們  起來
Come on, sweetheart. Stop sandbaggin' it. Now get up.
快起來!
Come on, get up.
你起不起來?
Would you get up?
不用浪費力氣了
Ni lo intentes.
也許你應用皮帶牽著她走
Maybe you better put her on a leash, agent man.
你有膽再一試!
Try it again...please.
別動!
Callate.
比利為什麼這樣緊張害怕?
What's got Billy so spooked?
我也不知道  少校
Can't say, Major.
一早就這樣了
Been acting squirrelly all morning.
他那鼻子是很奇怪的
That damn nose of his...it's weird.
是什麼  比利?
What is it? Billy.
你沒問題吧?
What the hell is wrong with you?
那樹上有些東西
There's something in those trees.
你看到上面有什麼?
Do you see anything? Up there ahead.
什麼也看不到
Nothing.
你認為是什麼?
What do you think?
我想可能沒什麼吧  少校
I guess it's nothing, Major.
好了!  別再掙扎了
Please! Please!
比利  搜查左邊!
Billy, break back.
麥克  右邊!
Back right.
這是...
What the...
這不是她的血
This isn't her blood.
你將他怎樣了!
What the hell did you do to him?
少校  你最好來看一看!
Major, you better take a look at this.
你找到霍金斯了嗎?
Did you find Hawkins?
我...我也不知道
I...I can't tell.
老天爺!
What in God's name?
我想那是霍金斯的血
I think it's Hawkins.
那他的屍體呢?
Where the hell is his body?
不知所蹤
There's no sign of it.
問她到底發生什麼事
Ask her what happened.
究竟發生什麼事?
你到底看到什麼?
他在哪裡?
我什麼也沒看到
-快說  -我沒看到他去了哪裡
他在哪裡  快說
什麼?
她說這叢林活過來抓走了他
She says the jungle...it just came alive and took him.
放屁!  她不是這樣說的
Bullshit! That's not what she said!
她說的完全沒有道理
What she said doesn't make any sense.
遊擊隊一直在追我們
Those sappers followed us...
亂說  他們在我們前面
Hell, they've been ahead of us!
這女人想趕到前面
This woman's been running us right to 'em !
別吵了
Hold it!
好了!
他們怎麼沒拿走他的  無線電或是武器?
Why didn't they take his radio or his weapon?
她為什麼沒逃走?
Why didn't she escape?
霍普!
Hopper.
什麼?
What?
他們像對付霍普一樣對霍金斯
They did the same thing to Jim Hopper.
搜尋霍金斯的屍體
I want Hawkins' body found.
掃蕩搜索隊形!
Sweep pattern.
往我們來的方向搜索  檢查這50公尺的範圍
Double back. 50 meters.
開始行動
Let's go.
出來吧  你們這些雜種
Come on in, you fuckers.
出來吧
Come on in.
我的武器在等待你們
Old Painless is waiting.
接觸敵人!
Sergeant!
出來吧  王八蛋!
Mother fucker! Fucker!
狗娘養的!  你這雜種
Mother fucker! You mother fucker!
發生什麼事?
What happened?
我看到它
I saw it.
你看到什麼?
You saw what?
我看到它
I saw it.
佈雷  身上沒有火藥痕跡
Blain. No powder burns,
沒有碎片
no shrapnel.
他的傷口是燒焦的
The wound's all fused, cauterized.
什麼東西會造成這樣的傷口
What the hell could have done this to a man?
麥克!  麥克  看著我!
Mac. Mac, look at me!
是誰做的?
Who did this?
我一點也不知道
I don't know, goddamn it.
我看到一些...一些東西
I saw s-something.
什麼也找不到
Not a thing,
一點痕跡也沒有
not a fucking trace.
沒有血跡...沒有屍體
No blood, no bodies.
我們什麼也沒打到!
We hit nothing.
狄龍  你最好快跟總部聯絡
Dillon...better get on the radio.
麥克!
Mac.
士官!
Sergeant!
是  長官
Yes, sir.
在山脊上佈置個防禦陣地
I want a defensive position above that ridge...
把所有爆炸品都準備好
mined with everything we've got.
把他放好  我們帶他一起走
Put him in his poncho. Take him with us.
我來辦!
I got him.
走吧!
Vamonos.
少校  我已經裝設好照明彈  手榴彈及地雷
Major...I set up flares, frags, and CIAymores.
沒有什麼能不碰到這些東西  進到這陣地來
Nothing's coming near this place without tripping on something.
謝謝你  士官
Thank you, sergeant.
麥克
Mac.
他是個好軍人
He was a good soldier.
他是...我的朋友
He was, um...my friend.
再見了  我的兄弟!
Good-bye, bro.
火焰一號  我重複
Blazer one, I repeat,
必須把我們撤離
extraction necessary.
再說一遍  火焰一號
Say again, Blazer one.
再說一遍
Say again.
你的要求不被接受
Request for extraction denied.
你的位置仍舊暴露在敵人的火力網下
Area is still compromised.
請前進到3000位置  我們在那裡接你們
Proceed to sector 3,000 for prisoner extraction. Priority, out.
下次聯絡時間是9:30
Next contact 0930.
知道了  火焰一號
Roger, Blazer one.
10:30聯絡
10:30 hours.
賤人
Damn bastards.
他們說我們的位置還太遠
They say we're still in too far,
他們不能冒險前來接我們
and they can't risk coming in.
我們是資產  狄龍
We're assets, Dillon.
可以犧牲的資產!
Expendable assets.
CIA就是這樣
It comes with the job.
這點我可以接受
I can accept it.
胡說  你跟我們一樣生氣
Bullshit. You're just like the rest of us.
直升機不會來這裡就是了
Shitload of good a chopper's gonna do us in here anyhow.
士官
Sergeant?
士官!  士官!
Sergeant! Sergeant!
今天誰攻擊我們?
Who hit us today?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只看到一個有偽裝的東西
I only saw one of them camouflaged.
他在那裡
He was there.
那對眼睛...忽然消失了
Those eyes disappeared.
你說什麼?
What was that?
那對眼睛  他們...他們消失不見了
Those eyes, they...they disappeared.
我只知道一件事  少校
I know one thing, Major.
我對準向它射擊
I drew down and fired straight at it.
我射了200輪以上
Capped off 200 rounds in the minigun...
我把所有子彈射光了
Full pack.
但是一點用處也沒有
Nothing...
這世上沒有什麼東西  在那個範圍內
nothing on this earth could have lived.
還能生存的
Not at that range.
麥克  你站第一班  然後去休息一會
Mac, you take first watch then you get some rest, OK?
問她看到什麼?  問她霍金斯怎麼了?
Ask her what she saw. Ask her what happened to Hawkins.
問她吧!
Go ahead, ask her.
你看到什麼了
叢林活過來把他抓走
還是那句話
Same fucking thing.
叢林活過來把他抓走
The jungle, it came alive and took him.
比利  你一定知道些什麼  到底是什麼?
Billy, you know something. What is it?
我感到害怕
I'm scared, Poncho.
放屁!  你不怕任何人的
Bullshit. You ain't afraid of no man.
外面有東西在等我們
There's something out there waiting for us...
而且並不是人
and it ain't no man.
我們全都會死
We're all gonna die.
這傢伙已經失去理智
The man's losing it. He's losing his cool.
只不過是有些敵人在附近
Nothing but a couple guys running around....
我們可以應付
and we gotta take 'em.
你還是不明白  狄龍
Still don't understand, Dillon, do you?
不管那是什麼
Whatever it is out there,
它殺了霍普
it killed Hopper...
現在它要殺死我們
and now it wants us.
我們又在一起了
Here we are again, bro...
只有你和我
just you and me.
一樣的月亮  一樣的叢林
Same kind of moon, same kind of jungle.
那晚我們喝酒來壯膽
Real number-ten night,
你還記得嗎?
remember?
整個部隊
Whole platoon...
32個人都被剁成肉醬
32 men chopped into meat...
除了你和我
and we walk out, just you and me.
再沒有別人
Nobody else.
我們是最好的戰士
Right on top of them.
這根本不算一回事
Not a scratch. Not a fucking scratch.
你知道不管是誰把你殺死
You know, whoever got you...
他會回來找我們
he'll come back again,
只要他敢回來
and when he does...
我會把你的名字刻在他身上
I'm going to cut your name into him.
什麼事?
What the hell is it?
麥克!
Mac!
這邊!
This way!
-你在那裡  麥克?  -在這邊
-Where are you? -Over here!
你在那裡?
Where are you?
麥克!
Mac!
麥克!  該死!
Mac! Fuck!
麥克  你在哪?
Mac, where are you?
老天!
Jesus.
捉逮到你了  賤人
I got you, mother fucker.
我殺死你
I killed you, you fuck.
老天  你殺了一隻豬
Jesus, you killed a pig.
你是不是應該找只大點的?
Think you could have found something bigger?
是啊  去你媽的!
Fuck you, Poncho. Fuck you.
那女人在那裡?
Where's the girl?
他媽的!
Aw, shit!
為什麼沒人看著她?
Why the hell wasn't anybody watching her?
她為什麼沒有逃走?
Why didn't she try to get away?
你看她  她嚇壞了!
Look at her. She's scared out of her mind.
少校  你最好來看看
Major, you better take a look at this.
佈雷的屍體不見了
Blain's body, it's gone.
它避過了我們設下的陷阱
It came in through the tripwires.
在我們面前把佈雷帶走
Took it right out from under our noses.
是那只豬誤觸陷阱
That boar had to set off a tripflare...
再沒有其它足印
because there ain't no other tracks.
怎麼有人能通過陷阱
How could anyone get through this...
帶走佈雷又不讓我們發覺?
and carry out Blain without us knowing it?
我是指他為什麼沒殺人呢?
Why didn't he try and kill one of us?
他來只是拿那屍體
He came to get the body.
他一次只殺一個
He's killing us one at a time.
就像獵人一樣
Like a hunter.
他是利用這些樹潛進來的
He's using the trees.
昨天你看到什麼?
Yesterday, what did you see?
你在浪費你的時間
You're wasting your time.
別再跟我們玩把戲
No more games.
我不知道它是什麼
I don't know what it was. It...
繼續
Go on.
它會變顏色
It changed colors
就像變色龍一樣
like the chameleon.
它利用這叢林
It uses the jungle.
你說他們是被蜥蜴殺死的?
Blain and Hawkins were killed by a lizard?
發什麼神經
That's a bullshit psych job.
外面最多只有兩三人在活動
There's 2 or 3 men out there.
去他媽的蜥蜴
Fucking lizard!
你叫什麼名字?
What's your name?
安娜
Anna.
Anna,
這東西在追捕我們
the thing is hunting us.
所有的人
All of us.
你明白嗎?
You know that.
你以為你在做什麼?
What the hell are you doing?
我們需要這裡的每個人
We'll need everyone.
我要帶她回去
l'm taking her back.
我們五分鐘後就要走
We leave in five minutes.
我們還不能走
We're not going yet.
聽著  救援部隊很快便到
Rendezvous is ten miles away.
你以為直升機會等我們嗎?
You think the chopper's going to wait?
狄龍  我們必須共同抵抗敵人
We make a stand now,
否則誰都不能活著出去
or nobody will be left.
還有一件事
There is something else.
那個大個子被殺的時候
When the big man was killed,
你一定弄傷了它
you must have wounded it.
它的血滴在樹葉上
Its blood was on the leaves.
如果它會流血  那麼我們就能殺掉它
If it bleeds, we can kill it.
小心
Look out.
你認為這童子軍玩意有效?
You really think this Boy Scout bullshit's gonna work?
它能看到那些金屬線
It can see tripwires.
但可能看不到這陷阱
Maybe it can't see this.
少廢話了  趕緊幫忙
Instead of complaining, maybe you should help.
怎麼你認為它一定會走這裡
What makes you think he'll come through here?
50碼半徑內的每棵樹上  都綁上了金屬線
The trees have tripwires every 50 yards.
這是剩下的唯一通路
This is the only way in.
當我還是小孩子時
When I was little,
我們找到一個男人
we found a man.
他看起來像被屠宰過
He looked like...like butchered.
村裡的老女人一直畫十字
The old women in the village crossed themselves...
祈禱著瘋狂  奇怪的禱詞
and whispered crazy things, such strange things.
魔鬼奉獻
只有在最熱的年份  才會發生這種事
Only in the hottest years this happens.
而今年也非常的熱
And this year, it grows hot.
我們開始找到那些男人
We begin finding our men.
有些被剝了皮
We found them sometimes without their skin
有時更可怕
and sometimes much, much worse.
魔鬼奉獻的意思是...
魔鬼把男人當作他的戰利品
means "the demon who makes trophies of man."
你下回要用什麼作餌  芝士?
What you gonna try next, cheese?
達奇!
Hey, Dutch. Dutch!
他媽的!
Shit!
捉到你了!  捉到了!
I got you, you mother! I got you!
我來追你!
I'm coming!
麥克!  麥克!
Mac! Mac!
帶他到直升機那裡
Get Ramirez to the chopper.
好的
Right.
等一下  達奇
Hold it.
我去追麥克
I'm going after Mac.
不像你的一貫作風  狄龍
That's not your style, Dillon.
我從你這學了些壞習慣
I picked up bad habits from you.
你們快走吧!
Get your people the hell out.
你不可能贏的  狄龍
You can't win this, Dillon.
也許我可以報仇
Maybe I can get even.
狄龍!
Dillon.
你只要叫那直升機等我和麥克回來就好了
Just hold onto that damn chopper.
他傷得很重  少校
He's busted up pretty bad, Major.
我可以捱得住
I can make it. I can make it.
帶走無線電  其它的都不要
Get the radio. Forget the rest.
好的!
Right!
走吧!  賓  我們走吧
Come on, Poncho.
老天
God!
高個子薩麗
"Long tall Sally"
她非常甜美
"she's built sweet!"
她什麼都有
"She got everything that Uncle John need"
寶貝
"Oh, baby"
"Baby"
給我點快樂...
"I'm gonna have me some fun"
轉過來
Turn around.
我在這裡
Over here.
麥克
Mac?
噓...
Shh.
麥克
Mac?
它在那裡  在那些樹上
Out there. Past them trees.
看得見嗎?
You see it?
我看到你了
I see you.
我看到了
I see it.
是的  我看到了
Yeah...I see it.
現在我們可以殺了它
You know, we can get this thing, Mac.
你慢慢爬過去接近它
You work your way down there toward him.
我在上頭逼近它後面  把它趕去你處
I'll get in back of him, flush him toward you.
當我趕那雜種時
When I flush the son of a bitch,
你就殺了它
you nail him.
我有個血海深仇要報
I got a score to settle.
我們都有仇要報
We've both got scores to settle.
趕快!  我們快走!
Come on! Quickly! Hurry up!
不要拿!  它沒殺你是因為你沒武裝
Don't. Leave it. It didn't kill you because you weren't armed.
對它來說太沒趣味!
No sport.
麥克!  麥克!
Mac. Mac.
好說
Anytime.
走吧!
Let's go.
比利!
Billy!
比利  我們走吧!
Billy, let's go!
給我武器  給我武器
Give me the weapon!
別拿!
No!
跑!  快走!
Run! Go!
去直升機那裡
Get to the chopper!
他媽的
Oh, shit!
它看不見我!
He couldn't see me.
流血吧  雜種!
Bleed, bastard.
你真的醜得很!
You're one ugly motherfucker.
這主意真差
Bad idea.
過來  過來啊!
Come on. Come on!
快啊  來啊!
Do it! Do it!
來殺我  我在這裡!  殺我啊!
Come on, Come on. Kill me! l'm here! Kill me!
來殺我!  我在這裡
l'm here! kill me!
Come on, Kill me! l'm here!
來啊  現在來殺我
Come on, do it now! Kill me!
你到底是什麼怪物
What the hell are you?